[
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99D_MSQ_01_Galahad_Resupply",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I didn't see any sign of them here.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Hm, neither did I. I suspect the Corrupted marched the captives off to one of their work camps to the north.\\n\\nWe can only hope their Heartgems protected them and they have not fallen. We must attempt rescue.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99D_MSQ_01_Yash_RescueWarden",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I'll handle the hounds. The path is clear for you.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "The way is clear? Amazing. I suppose this is why Yonas holds you in such high esteem. Well deserved, it seems.\\n\\nBut I cannot leave without the others. I swore to them I would get them out of this mess.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99D_MSQ_01_Judithe_RescueWarden",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Yes, and you should go join him.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Those are welcome tidings. I had feared our time as Soulwardens was going to be short-lived.\\n\\nPerhaps we have a chance against the Corrupted , after all.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99D_MSQ_01_Pedro_RescueWarden",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Head for the road, then to the outpost.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "I guess that's straightforward enough. I tried to run twice before, and they weren't too gentle bringing me back.\\n\\nHere's hoping third time brings me luck!",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99D_MSQ_03_Yonas_ThorpeNews",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Thorpe? He was captain of the ship that brought me here.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Ah, a story begins to unfold… the fact he is a new leader among the Corrupted… it makes sense.\\n\\nWhile you have worked to become a Soulwarden and defend against Corruption, your Captain has taken a much darker path.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99D_MSQ_03_Yonas_Tempest",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Thorpe mentioned an 'Isabella'?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Isabella… that name has not been spoken in a long time. \\n\\nPerhaps this is the Tempest? How curious that Thorpe knows her given name.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99D_MSQ_05_Galahad_westoutpost",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"It was a risk, but worth trying.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "And I have no intention of backing down on the plan. I obviously did not intend for Yash to be cut off, but I stand ready to make amends.\\n\\nLead the charge across the bridge, Soulwarden. Yonas and I will follow.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99D_MSQ_05_Yash_ExchangeInfo",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Good work. There are no Corrupted defending it?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Not the outpost; but they patrol it from the nearby forts. We'll need to put those forts on the defensive. \\n\\nI was working myself up to stage an the attack alone, but... I think your presence improves the chances of success.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99D_MSQ_07_Ofusa_RescuePortal",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Stay strong. We can do this.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "With you here, my hopes are renewed, we can't allow them to take any more captive.\\n\\nOur strength lies in the trust we have with our team.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99D_MSQ_07_Jacquet_RescuePortal",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I understand, but we must fight on.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Yes… yes. You're right, I must stand firm against the fallen, even if they are former friends. \\n\\nWe must defeat them to protect those of us who remain.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99D_MSQ_07_Yash_Portal",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"There must be a way to close it.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Perhaps… on the other side, but… I mean, I consider myself brave, but that would seem to venturing into the literal gates of hell.\\n\\nAnd what, we leave Commander Thorpe continue his campaign here?",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99D_MSQ_09_Grace_Supplies",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Yes, we just need to get Yonas healed.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Indeed, lucky you had a smuggler like your friend Grace running supplies. Those supply lines were about as safe as a den of vipers!\\n\\nJust want it on record I'm doing my part, especially if it comes to counting spoils.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99D_MSQ_09_Yonas_Medicine",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"You did, and you delivered.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "We did, didn't we…? Alright then, you all can stop hovering over me with bandages and potions. I don't need them.\\n\\nI'm an old soldier, and I've healed from worse than this. Just need some rest.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99D_MSQ_09_Yash_Medicine",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"He won't take it.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Bah, give it to me! I'll get the old man to listen to reason, and if not, I'll pour it down his throat when he's sleeping.\\n\\nWe need to get him well enough to get him back to Caer Dun.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99D_MSQ_10_Galahad_DefendCaerDun",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I heard Morgaine was here.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "She was. The sorceress wasted not a moment before arguing with Sun about the Angry Earth.\\n\\nMorgaine left in a huff, but Sun's gone after her. My focus now is to ensure the Wardens here were not too discouraged.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99D_MSQ_10_Yonas_CaerDun",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Why are you here?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Because you're needed back at Eastmarch. Herbalist Sun Fuchun awaits you there, and she's distraught.\\n\\nCan't say I fully understand, but that's the message, and now I must rest. Can't let Galahad do more work than me.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    }
]
